这个App，我们使用了大饼干模型
In this app, we see an example of a
将网络传输合并到一块
defragmented network traffic that uses the big cookie model. All
所有的反复的传输绑到一起
the repeating transfers have been bundled together, and all
UI交互引起的间歇传输
the intermittent transfers have been
由主动预读取所取代
largely replaced with aggressive prefetching.
很显然，你不能完全地预测用户可能需要的信息
Obviously, you usually can't entirely predict what data users
并且也不能忽略客户端或者服务器端
might need, nor can you ignore either client or service
需要被同步的变化
site changes the need to be synchronized. You can
你可以最小化无线电传输的次数
aim to minimize the number of radio state transitions through
除了将不是急需的数据和由用户或者服务器
a combination of aggressive prefetching in addition to batching
引起的急需数据成批一起请求，
and queueing any transfers that aren't time critical and
还可以利用预读取技术
bundling these with user initiated time critical transfers, or
those initiated from the server. If we compare the impact
如果把这个大饼干模型和之前的
on the radio of the big cookie model compared
小饼干模型进行比较的话，可以发现
to the previous on demand approach, you can see it's
现在的空闲状态几乎是占三分之二时间
now idle nearly two thirds of the time. Even
无线电活动状态的百分比显著减少
the active radio percentage has significantly dropped, thanks to improved
一次传输大量数据改进了下载效率
download efficiency as a result of transmitting more data in one shot